addynamix.com 2008-12-17

# AdDynamix

|   |  |   
---  
|  |    
---  
   
**PENNYWEB, INC. DBA ADDYNAMIX  
PRIVACY STATEMENT **

Pennyweb, Inc. is a TRUSTe licensee. The TRUSTe program and certification covers only information that is collected and disseminated through this Web site and does not cover any services or products or information that may be collected through software downloaded from the site, <http://www.addynamix.com/>. 

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should first contact Privacy by, Los Angeles Center Studios, 1201 W. 5th Street, Suite T300, Los Angeles, CA 90017. If they do not receive acknowledgment of their inquiry or their inquiry is not satisfactorily addressed, they should then contact TRUSTe through the [TrusteWatchdogDisputeResolutionProcess](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php) TRUSTe will serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve users concerns. 

Pennyweb, Inc. is committed to protecting the privacy of consumers, publishers, and advertisers, and to do our part to maintain the integrity of the Internet.

**Notification of Changes** If Pennyweb, Inc. decides to change its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.

**Disclaimer:** Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

**Client Data (i.e. Web Publishers and Advertisers)** Non-Personally Identifiable Client Data. Pennyweb, Inc. does not collect non-personally identifiable information from our clients. Non-personally identifiable information is also known as "demographic" data and includes information such as age, gender, and income range. Personally Identifiable Client Data Pennyweb, Inc. collects personally identifiable information from all websites (and specifically their owners) wishing to join our network. The collection of this information is a part of normal business practice. Clients wishing to join the Pennyweb, Inc. advertising network will be asked to provide personally identifiable data through the host sign-up and registration process at our web site. Examples of personally identifiable data that may be requested include name, address, phone number, e-mail address, social security number, tax ID number, etc. Pennyweb, Inc. will never request or collect data from a client on subject areas including sexual orientation, political or religious affiliations, or medical data.

Pennyweb, Inc. does not use any personally identifiable data about a client for profiling purposes. All personally identifiable information that Pennyweb, Inc. collects from clients is principally intended for administrative needs (e.g., accounting and pay-out), for which purpose such data are required. Periodically Pennyweb, Inc. may desire to communicate with our network of hosts via email newsletters or other avenues to offer strategic marketing information and other communications to assist in business related activities. In such instances Pennyweb, Inc. will access clients' personally identifiable information. In the event that a client of Pennyweb, Inc. wishes not to have their personally identifiable information used for the aforementioned purposes, those clients can elect to opt-out. For more information on opting-out please see the "Client Choice Concerning Data Collection" section below. All personally identifiable data provided by individual clients will be kept in strict confidence by Pennyweb, Inc. and will be treated with the same level of respect and care that Pennyweb, Inc. treats its other proprietary information and trade secrets. Pennyweb, Inc. does not sell, rent, exchange or barter any personally identifiable information to or with any third party for financial gain or marketing purposes. Pennyweb, Inc. may, from time to time, provide such information to certain third-party administrative vendors for efficiency purposes in providing administrative services such as billing, delivery and payouts. Any third-party vendor so used, will be required to enter into a confidentiality and non-disclosure agreement with Pennyweb, Inc. in accordance with the policies stated here.

**Client Choice Concerning Data Collection** Personally Identifiable Client Data - Opt-Out Because Pennyweb, Inc. is a strong proponent of online privacy we are committed to making sure that clear notice and choice is provided to all clients before any personally identifiable data are used for any purposes other than for what was originally intended. When a client joins Pennyweb, Inc.'s network and registers for Pennyweb, Inc.'s services, personally identifiable information is required as a part of doing business. Pennyweb, Inc.'s primary intent in collecting personally identifiable information is for use in administrative purposes including accounting and payouts.

View deatiled inforamtion regarding Pennyweb, Inc. Data Collection practices.  
  
**Web Site Tracking** The Pennyweb web site servers use log files. These logs include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, referring pages, platform type, and date/time stamp, to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.  
|    
---  
The Pennyweb web site uses session cookies to maintain a users session state while using the online reporting feature. Session cookies are removed from the users computer upon exiting the browser and are not used to collect personally identifiable information. If a user chooses to decline these session cookies, the online reporting feature will not be usable. **

Security Precautions

**

Pennyweb, Inc. makes every effort to maintain the security of its network and the data we collect. Any data that is stored on Pennyweb, Inc.'s server is treated as proprietary and confidential and is not available to the public. Pennyweb, Inc. has a strict internal security policy with respect to the confidentiality of customer and other data, limiting access only to those employees or third parties who have a need to know such information for the purpose of effectively delivering Pennyweb, Inc. products and services.   
**  
****Access to Data** Pennyweb, Inc. allows clients who have provided personally identifiable data, access to their data to ensure that it is correct and to make any changes at anytime through their Pennyweb customer online account by sending an email to Privacy or calling (888) 867-3669.

**Pennyweb Network** Pennyweb and Client Website Privacy Policy Statements In accordance with the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) Pennyweb, Inc. requests that website publishers belonging to our advertising network create privacy policy statements. Pennyweb, Inc. asks that websites in our net work comply with Online Privacy Alliance (OPA) guidelines by disclosing any and all information that is being collected from Internet consumers on their website, including data gathered from banners and other forms of advertising being served on their website. We also ask that they provide Internet consumers with conspicuous access to their statements.

**Children's Privacy**

As of April 21, 2000 the children's Online Privacy Protection Act became effective. The regulations apply to the online collection of personal information from children under the age of 13. Pennyweb, Inc. is very sensitive to the issue of children's privacy and makes every effort to protect the privacy of children using the Internet. Pennyweb, Inc.'s web site, products, and services are not developed for or directed at children. Our policy is not to permit anyone under the age of 13 to do business with us. If you believe your child has provided Pennyweb, Inc. with any personally identifiable data by registering at Pennyweb, Inc.'s web site, please contact Privacy to have them removed. We also request that all websites using our advertising network disclose in their privacy statements any and all information regarding the collection of information from children. **

Website Testimonials

**

If you choose to post a testimonial on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these testimonials. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these testimonials.

**Involvement with Industry Partners** Pennyweb, Inc. is committed to helping protect consumer privacy on the Internet and, as such, we actively monitor consumer privacy issues. Further evidence of Pennyweb, Inc.'s commitment to consumer privacy is our involvement with the following privacy advocacy groups:

Network Advertising Initiative Pennyweb, Inc. fully supports and endorses the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI). The NAI is a group of third party network advertisers committed to increasing consumer confidence and contributing to the growth of electronic commerce. We are committed to providing consumers with a clear explanation of what data we collect, how we use them, and why the use of data can benefit consumer's experience online. For more information about the Network Advertising Alliance please go to [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

The Online Privacy Alliance Pennyweb, Inc. fully supports and endorses the Online Privacy Alliance (OPA). The OPA is a cross-industry group of more than 90 global companies and associations who have joined efforts to introduce and promote business-wide actions that create an environment of trust and foster the protection of individuals' privacy online. For more information about the Online Privacy Alliance, please go to [http://www.privacyalliance.org](http://www.privacyalliance.org/).

BBBOnline Pennyweb, Inc. is a member of the BBBOnline. For more information on the specifics of their respective policies and programs please go to [http://www.bbbonline.com](http://www.bbbonline.com/).

TRUSTe Pennyweb, Inc. is a TRUSTe licensee. For more information on the specifics of their respective policies and programs please go to [http://www.truste.com](http://www.truste.com/) **

Opt-Out of Email Communications from Pennyweb, Inc.

** To opt-out of email communications from Pennyweb, Inc., including promotional, marketing, and/or advertising emails, email Privacy with the word "UNSUBSCRIBE" in the message body.

**Changing Personally Identifiable Information with Pennyweb, Inc.** Advertisers or Publishers who have filled out any of the online forms for more information or for registration with Pennyweb Network can change their personally identifiable information by emailing Privacy or calling **Toll Free** (888) 867-3669. Current Publishers can update their information by contacting the AffiliateNetwork or by calling Toll Free (888) 867-3669. We will contact you via email or phone to confirm that your information has been updated.

**Contacting Us**

For more information or if you have questions or concerns regarding Pennyweb, Inc.'s Privacy Statement, please send an e-mail to Privacy , or you can send correspondence to the following address: 

**Privacy  
**AdDynamix  
Los Angeles Center Studios  
1201 W. 5th Street  
Suite T300  
Los Angeles, CA 90017.

Effective: November 2004   

  |  |
